Shahmeer Ahmad

Flutter Developer

My Contact

shahmeerahmad1435@gmail.com

(+923041628668

Bahawalpur

Hard Skill

- Flutter
- Dart
- Github / Bitbucket Push / Git Push
- Google Maps
- Socket Programming
- Push Notifications
- State Management
- API Integration
- Firebase
- Android Development
- Deployment of Application
- Design Patterns
- WebRTC
- Flutter IoT
- WebPack
- Laravel(API CRUD)
- UI/U>
- Android Studio & XCode

Soft Skill

- Observation
- · Decision making
- Communication
- Clean Architecture
- Project Management
- Team Management
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

- The Islamia University of Bahawalpur (RYK)
 Bacholar's in Computer Science
 Completed in 2022
- The Millat Collage of Bahawalpur Intermediat in Computer Science Completed in 2018

About Me

I'm 24 and have worked as a Flutter Developer for a smaller company, in an agile team, working primarily on Hybrid apps, with Flutter and Dart.BS graduate in Computer Science. Application-based knowledge of compatible application designing according to the user requirement.

Professional Experience

ENTSPOS Developers Inc. | Flutter Developer 2019 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Produce clean, efficient code based on specifications
- Verify and deploy programs and systems
- · Troubleshoot, debug and upgrade existing software
- Recommend and execute improvements
- · Verify and deploy programs and systems
- · Integrate software components and third-party programs
- Gather and evaluate user feedback
- Work with developers to design algorithms and flowcharts

Mahar Technologies | Junior Flutter Developer 2021 – 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Work on a Food App
- Upgrade existing software

VirtueNetz | Junior Flutter Developer & Laravel Intern 2020 – 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Learn Laravel CRUD and API Building
- Upgrade existing Website
- Build Flutter App from Scratch
- Team & Project Management

Extra-curricular Activities

2020 – 2021 Google Developer Student Club Lead

2017 - 2017 Office Assitant, Millat Collage Ahmedpur East